bytesforall.com 2016-11-02

# Privacy Policy « ThemeFrame

This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give when you use this website.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from Oct 28, 2009.

### What we collect

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences.

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

Internal record keeping.  
We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information. Consumers can have this information corrected by visiting us at http://forum.bytesforall.com/usercp.php.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by writing to us.

With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to or email us.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
